Henry A. Grunwald Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Time, inc. Editorial Files, 1941-2005 (Box 98-196)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1987 (Box 98-118)
    - 1982, "A-P" miscellaneous, (11 folders) (Box 113)
    - 1982, "R-Z" miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 114)
    - 1983, "A-R" miscellaneous, (12 folders) (Box 114)
    - 1983, "S-Z" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 115)
    - 1984, "A-P" miscellaneous, (10 folders) (Box 115)
    - 1984, "R-Z" miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 116)
    - 1985, "A-Z" miscellaneous, (12 folders) (Box 116)
    - 1986, "A-W" miscellaneous, (14 folders) (Box 117)
    - 1987, "A-Z" miscellaneous, (8 folders) (Box 118)
  - Staff Files, 1969-1987 (Box 118-148)
    Correspondence and memoranda among employees of Time Magazine or Time, inc. This material consists chiefly of photocopies of documents held in the Time, inc. archive.
    Arranged chronologically, then alphabetically by name of staff member therein.
    - 1969-1972
      - General staff (Box 118)
      - Domestic correspondents (Box 118)
      - Foreign correspondents (Box 118)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 118)
      - Barr, Don (Box 118)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 118)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 118)
      - Donovan, Hedley (Box 118)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 119)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 119)
      - Luce, Henry, III (Box 119)
      - Vega, Marylois (Box 119)
    - 1973
      - Miscellaneous staff (Box 119)
      - Henry A. Grunwald's staff (Box 119)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 119)
      - Donovan, Hedley (Box 119)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 119)
      - Gordon, Leah (Box 119)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 119)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 119)
      - Korn, Jerry (Box 119)
      - Sidey, Hugh (Box 119)
    - 1974
      - Miscellaneous staff, (3 folders) (Box 119)
      - General staff (Box 119)
      - Barr, Don (Box 119)
      - Birnbaum, Jesse (Box 120)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 120)
      - Donovan, Hedley, (2 folders) (Box 120)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 120)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 120)
      - Vega, Marylois (Box 120)
      - Wires, domestic (Box 120)
    - 1975
      - Miscellaneous staff, (2 folders) (Box 120)
      - General staff (Box 120)
      - Barr, Don (Box 120)
      - Cave, Ray (Box 120)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 120)
      - Donovan, Hedley, (2 folders) (Box 121)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 121)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 121)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 121)
      - Jackson, R. Edward (Box 121)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 121)
      - Vega, Marylois (Box 121)
    - 1976
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-M", (12 folders) (Box 121)
      - Miscellaneous staff "N-Z", (8 folders) (Box 122)
      - Henry A. Grunwald's staff (Box 122)
      - Barr, Don (Box 122)
      - Birnbaum, Jesse (Box 122)
      - Cave, Ray (Box 122)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 122)
      - Donovan, Hedley, (2 folders) (Box 122)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 122)
      - Elson, John T. (Box 122)
      - Friedrich, Otto (Box 122)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 122)
      - Gordon, Leah (Box 122)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 122)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 122)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 123)
    - 1977
      - Miscellaneous staff "B-Y", (8 folders) (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous staff, Jan.-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 123)
      - General staff (Box 123)
      - Managing editors (Box 123)
      - Ajemian, Robert (Box 124)
      - Barrett, Laurence I. (Box 124)
      - Bernard, Walter (Box 124)
      - Birnbaum, Jesse (Box 124)
      - Brack, Reginald Jr. (Box 124)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 124)
      - Cave, Ray, (2 folders) (Box 124)
      - Church, George J. (Box 124)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 124)
      - Donovan, Hedley, (3 folders) (Box 124)
      - Duffy, Martha (Box 124)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 124)
      - Durniak, John (Box 124)
      - Elson, John T. (Box 124)
      - Ferenbaugh, Dorothy (Box 124)
      - Foote, Timothy (Box 124)
      - Friedrich, Otto (Box 124)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 124)
      - Gordon, Leah (Box 125)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 125)
      - Heiskell, Andrew (Box 125)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 125)
      - Jaroff, Leon (Box 125)
      - Kanfer, Stefan (Box 125)
      - Korn, Jerry (Box 125)
      - Kriss, Ronald (Box 125)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B., (2 folders) (Box 125)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 125)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 125)
      - Merrill, David (Box 125)
      - Steed, Bob (Box 125)
      - Sweeney, Bob (Box 125)
      - Tinnin, David B. (Box 125)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 125)
      - Zim, Marvin (Box 125)
    - 1978
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-Z", (11 folders) (Box 126)
      - Airey, Norman (Box 126)
      - Bear, Charley (Box 126)
      - Cave, Ray, Jan.-Sept., (3 folders) (Box 126)
      - Cave, Ray, Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 127)
      - Clarke, Fred (Box 127)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 127)
      - Donovan, Hedley, (2 folders) (Box 127)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 127)
      - Ferenbaugh, Dorothy (Box 127)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 127)
      - Gordon, Leah (Box 127)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 127)
      - Heiskell, Andrew (Box 127)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 127)
      - Keylor, Arthur W. (Box 127)
      - Korn, Jerry (Box 127)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 128)
      - Lubar, Robert (Box 128)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 128)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 128)
      - Rosen, Clare Mead (Box 128)
      - Shepley, James R. (Box 128)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 128)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 128)
      - Sweeney, Bob (Box 128)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 128)
    - 1979
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-N", (7 folders) (Box 128)
      - Miscellaneous staff "O-W", (3 folders) (Box 129)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 129)
      - Bear, Charley (Box 129)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 129)
      - Brown, Dale (Box 129)
      - Cave, Ray, (11 folders) (Box 129)
      - Donovan, Hedley (Box 130)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 130)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 130)
      - Gordon, Leah (Box 130)
      - Graves, Ralph, (2 folders) (Box 130)
      - Heiskell, Andrew (Box 130)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 130)
      - Korn, Jerry (Box 130)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 130)
      - Lubar, Robert (Box 130)
      - Manley, Joan D. (Box 130)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 130)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 130)
      - Rogin, Gilbert (Box 130)
      - Rosen, Clare Mead (Box 130)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 130)
      - Shepley, James R. (Box 131)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 131)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 131)
    - 1980
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-Z", (9 folders) (Box 131)
      - General staff (Box 131)
      - Ajemian, Robert (Box 131)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 131)
      - Bear, Charley (Box 131)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 131)
      - Brown, Dale (Box 131)
      - Cave, Ray, (8 folders) (Box 132)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 132)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 132)
      - Graves, Ralph, (10 folders) (Box 132)
      - Heiskell, Andrew (Box 132)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 132)
      - Korn, Jerry (Box 132)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 132)
      - Lubar, Robert (Box 133)
      - Manley, Joan D. (Box 133)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 133)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 133)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 133)
      - Rosen, Clare Mead (Box 133)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 133)
      - Shepley, James R. (Box 133)
      - Steed, Bob (Box 133)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 133)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 133)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 133)
    - 1981
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-W", (8 folders) (Box 133)
      - General staff (Box 133)
      - Bear, Charley (Box 134)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 134)
      - Cave, Ray, (2 folders) (Box 134)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 134)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 134)
      - Gart, Murray J. (Box 134)
      - Graves, Ralph, (2 folders) (Box 134)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 134)
      - Jaroff, Leon (Box 134)
      - Korn, Jerry (Box 134)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 134)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 134)
      - Maness, David (Box 134)
      - Manley, Joan D. (Box 134)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 134)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 134)
      - Rosen, Clare Mead (Box 134)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 135)
      - Steed, Bob (Box 135)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 135)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 135)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 135)
    - 1982
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-Z", (11 folders) (Box 135)
      - General staff (Box 135)
      - Managing editors (Box 135)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 135)
      - Bear, Charley (Box 135)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 135)
      - Burgheim, Richard (Box 136)
      - Cave, Ray, (2 folders) (Box 136)
      - Constable, George (Box 136)
      - Crutcher, Lawrence M. (Box 136)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 136)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 136)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 136)
      - Grum, Clifford J. (Box 136)
      - Howell, Barbara Thompson (Box 136)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 136)
      - Jaroff, Leon (Box 136)
      - Kerr, Jeanne (Box 136)
      - Korn, Jerry (Box 136)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 136)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 136)
      - Maness, David (Box 136)
      - Manley, Joan D. (Box 136)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 136)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 137)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 137)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 137)
      - Ryan, Pat (Box 137)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 137)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 137)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 137)
    - 1983
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-R", (8 folders) (Box 137)
      - Miscellaneous staff "S-Z", (2 folders) (Box 138)
      - General staff (Box 138)
      - Managing editors (Box 138)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 138)
      - Bear, Charley (Box 138)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 138)
      - Burgheim, Richard (Box 138)
      - Cave, Ray, (5 folders) (Box 138)
      - Constable, George (Box 138)
      - Crutcher, Lawrence M. (Box 138)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 138)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 138)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 138)
      - Grum, Clifford J. (Box 138)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 138)
      - Jaroff, Leon (Box 138)
      - Kerr, Jeanne (Box 139)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 139)
      - Maness, David (Box 139)
      - Manley, Joan D. (Box 139)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 139)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 139)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 139)
      - Rogin, Gilbert (Box 139)
      - Rukeyser, William S., (2 folders) (Box 139)
      - Ryan, Pat (Box 139)
      - Steed, Bob (Box 139)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 139)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 139)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 139)
    - 1984
      - Miscellaneous staff "B-G", (4 folders) (Box 139)
      - Miscellaneous staff "H-Z", (7 folders) (Box 140)
      - General staff (Box 140)
      - Managing editors (Box 140)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 140)
      - Bear, Charley (Box 140)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 140)
      - Cave, Ray, (5 folders) (Box 140)
      - Crutcher, Lawrence M. (Box 140)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 140)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 141)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 141)
      - Hiland, Bruce (Box 141)
      - Jaroff, Leon (Box 141)
      - Kerr, Jeanne (Box 141)
      - Kriss, Ronald (Box 141)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 141)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 141)
      - Maness, David (Box 141)
      - McCandless, Carolyn (Box 141)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 141)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 141)
      - Nicholas, Nick Jr. (Box 141)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 141)
      - Rogin, Gilbert (Box 141)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 141)
      - Ryan, Pat (Box 141)
      - Sheppe, P. Peter (Box 141)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 141)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 141)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 141)
    - 1985
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-W", (12 folders) (Box 142)
      - General staff (Box 142)
      - Managing editors (Box 142)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 142)
      - Barnet, Bruce (Box 142)
      - Bingle, Jay (Box 142)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 142)
      - Constable, George (Box 142)
      - Cox, Tony (Box 142)
      - Crutcher, Lawrence M. (Box 143)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 143)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 143)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 143)
      - Hiland, Bruce (Box 143)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 143)
      - Kriss, Ronald (Box 143)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 143)
      - Lalli, Frank (Box 143)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 143)
      - Maness, David (Box 143)
      - McManus, Jason (Box 143)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 143)
      - Nicholas, Nick Jr. (Box 143)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 143)
      - Rogin, Gilbert (Box 143)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 143)
      - Ryan, Pat (Box 143)
      - Sheppe, P. Peter (Box 143)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 143)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 143)
      - Taber, George M. (Box 143)
      - Talbott, Strobe (Box 143)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 143)
    - 1986
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-W", (9 folders) (Box 144)
      - General staff (Box 144)
      - Managing editors (Box 144)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 144)
      - Barnet, Bruce (Box 144)
      - Brack, Reginald Jr. (Box 144)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 144)
      - Cave, Ray (Box 144)
      - Daniels, Judith (Box 144)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 144)
      - Demaree, Allan T. (Box 144)
      - Di Sapio, Rosemarie (Box 144)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 144)
      - Gardner, Marty (Box 144)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 145)
      - Guttman, William (Box 145)
      - Hiland, Bruce (Box 145)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 145)
      - Jones, Landon Y. (Box 145)
      - Kerr, Jeanne (Box 145)
      - Kriss, Ronald (Box 145)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 145)
      - McManus, Jason, (2 folders) (Box 145)
      - Muller, Henry (Box 145)
      - Mulvoy, Mark (Box 145)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 145)
      - Nicholas, Nick Jr. (Box 145)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 145)
      - Rogin, Gilbert (Box 145)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 146)
      - Ryan, Pat (Box 146)
      - Stolley, Richard B. (Box 146)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 146)
      - Talbott, Strobe (Box 146)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 146)
    - 1987
      - Miscellaneous staff "A-W", (6 folders) (Box 146)
      - General staff (Box 146)
      - Managing editors (Box 146)
      - Banks, Louis (Box 146)
      - Barnet, Bruce (Box 146)
      - Brack, Reginald Jr. (Box 146)
      - Brine, Ruth (Box 146)
      - Cave, Ray (Box 146)
      - Daniels, Judith (Box 146)
      - Davidson, Ralph (Box 146)
      - Demaree, Allan T. (Box 146)
      - Di Sapio, Rosemarie (Box 147)
      - Duncan, Richard (Box 147)
      - Geisenheimer, Susan (Box 147)
      - Graves, Ralph (Box 147)
      - Guerette, Donald R. (Box 147)
      - Guttman, William (Box 147)
      - Jamieson, Edward L. (Box 147)
      - Jones, Landon Y. (Box 147)
      - Kriss, Ronald (Box 147)
      - Kunhardt, Philip B. (Box 147)
      - Loeb, Marshall (Box 147)
      - Meigher, S. Christopher, III (Box 147)
      - Miller, Robert (Box 147)
      - Muller, Henry, (2 folders) (Box 147)
      - McManus, Jason, (2 folders) (Box 147)
      - Mulvoy, Mark (Box 147)
      - Munro, J. Richard (Box 147)
      - Nicholas, Nick Jr. (Box 147)
      - Prendergast, Curtis (Box 147)
      - Rogin, Gilbert (Box 147)
      - Rukeyser, William S. (Box 147)
      - Ryan, Pat (Box 147)
      - Sutton, Kelso (Box 148)
      - Talbott, Strobe (Box 148)
      - Wilson, Donald M. (Box 148)
  - Subject Files, 1949-1987 (Box 149-187)
    Correspondence, notes, clippings, and other materials, chiefly concerning events, meetings, and publications. This material consists chiefly of photocopies of documents held in the Time, inc. archive.
    Arranged chronologically, then alphabetically by subject therein.
    - 1949-1962
      - Matthews, T.S., memoranda, 1949 (Box 149)
      - Chambers, Whitacker, 1950s (Box 149)
      - Life magazine, unused articles, 1950s (Box 149)
      - "The American Woman," 1952, (2 folders) (Box 149)
      - Miscellaneous cover stories, 1952 (Box 149)
      - Luce, Henry Robinson, letters, memoranda, and speeches, 1953-1966, (2 folders) (Box 149)
      - Luce, Henry Robinson, letters, memoranda, and speeches, 1953-1966, (1 folder) (Box 150)
      - "Issue of the Week," 1954 (Box 150)
      - Europe trip, May 1958 (Box 150)
      - Music, 1960s (Box 150)
      - Europe trip, Aug.-Sept. 1962 (Box 150)
      - Research and development, 1962-1963 (Box 150)
    - 1963-1964
      - Grunwald, Henry A., "Report on Television," 1963 (Box 150)
      - Time magazine fortieth anniversary, 1963, (2 folders) (Box 150)
      - Time magazine fortieth anniversary, 1963, (4 folders) (Box 151)
      - "The Quality of Life behind the Soviet Statistics," Fortune, March, 1964 (Box 151)
    - 1965-1967
      - KOGO-TV, San Diego, Calif., 1965 (Box 151)
      - Vietnam, 1965-1967 (Box 151)
      - Appointment as assistant managing editor, 1966 (Box 151)
      - Cover correspondence and artists, 1966-1968 (Box 151)
      - McLuhan, Marshall, 1966 (Box 151)
      - "The Story of Great Music," 1966 (Box 151)
      - Luce, Henry Robinson, death, 1967 (Box 151)
    - 1968
      - Appointment as managing editor, (2 folders) (Box 152)
      - Behavior section, Time magazine (Box 152)
      - Henry R. Luce Memorial Fund (Box 152)
      - Time magazine extra supplement (Box 152)
    - 1969
      - "The American Century" and United States mission in the world, research, (2 folders) (Box 152)
      - Articles on Time magazine and Grunwald (Box 152)
      - "Newsweek: Fact from Opinion" (Box 152)
      - "On Admitting Error about Vietnam" (Box 152)
      - Studies of Time magazine (Box 153)
    - 1970-1972
      - Black issue, 1970 (Box 153)
      - European edition, 1970-1973 (Box 153)
      - Analysis of public opinion polls, 1971-1972 (Box 153)
      - Supplements, 1971-1972 (Box 153)
      - Congressional symposium, 1972 (Box 153)
      - Equality, 1972 (Box 153)
      - "An Opening in Europe: Report of the European Task Force," 1972 (Box 153)
      - Sex section, 1972 (Box 153)
      - "What To Do About... " 1972 (Box 153)
      - Women's issue, 1972 (Box 153)
    - 1973
      - Coffey, Richard E., "A View of the News: a One-man Survey" (Box 153)
      - Europe trip, Mar.-Apr. (Box 153)
      - Time, inc. Energy Conference, 12-15 Apr. (Box 153)
      - Time magazine fiftieth anniversary, (2 folders) (Box 154)
      - Watergate Affair (Box 154)
    - 1974
      - California trip, 11-12 Feb. (Box 154)
      - Harvard University and Massachusetts Institute of Technology seminar (Box 154)
      - Idea file (Box 154)
      - Monday-Friday work week (Box 154)
      - Newsweek notes (Box 154)
      - Press shield legislation (Box 154)
      - Time, inc. Energy Conference, 28 April-1 May, (2 folders) (Box 154)
      - Time magazine notes (Box 154)
      - Tour of southern states, 13-18 Oct. (Box 154)
      - Trilateral Commission (Box 154)
    - 1975
      - "America at 200," Founders' Day Convocation, New York University, New York, N.Y. (Box 155)
      - Bad english memorandum (Box 155)
      - Bicentennial, (2 folders) (Box 155)
      - Canadian issue (Box 155)
      - Century Club address, 10 Jan. (Box 155)
      - Commencement address, Nightingale-Bamford School, New York, N.Y. (Box 155)
      - Europe trip, Apr.-May (Box 155)
      - Future of magazines (Box 155)
      - Ideas file (Box 155)
      - Man of the Year (Box 155)
      - Money speeches and essays (Box 155)
      - Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), tapes (Box 155)
      - Presidential candidates (Box 155)
      - Soviet Union trip, May-June, (2 folders) (Box 155)
      - Studies of Time magazine (Box 155)
      - Time, inc. Middle East newstour, 16-31 Jan., (2 folders) (Box 155)
      - Tour of western states, Nov.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 156)
    - 1976
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Fellowship in Economics Journalism at Princeton University (Box 156)
      - Bicentennial, (2 folders) (Box 156)
      - Bumpers, Dale Leon (Box 156)
      - Europe trip, Apr. (Box 156)
      - Houston, Tex., trip, 7-8 Nov. (Box 156)
      - New York Conference on the Media and the Law, 21-23 May (Box 156)
      - Notes from managing editors (Box 156)
      - Presidential campaign coverage (Box 156)
      - Reorganization (Box 156)
      - Time magazine and Newsweek analysis (Box 156)
      - Time magazine and Newsweek board of directors (Box 156)
      - Time, inc. employee strike, (3 folders) (Box 156)
      - Time, inc. Leadership Conference, Washington, D.C., 26-27 Sept., (1 folder) (Box 156)
      - Time, inc. Leadership Conference, Washington, D.C., 26-27 Sept., (3 folders) (Box 157)
    - 1977
      - Africa trip, 5-25 May, (4 folders) (Box 157)
      - Appointment as corporate editor, (4 folders) (Box 157)
      - Begin, Menachem, Time magazine cover, May (Box 157)
      - Kissinger, Henry, party, 4 Feb. (Box 157)
      - Legal department (Box 157)
      - Media and Business Seminar, Princeton, N.J. (Box 157)
      - "Mood of America" speech, Washington, D.C., 16 Oct. (Box 158)
      - New York World prospectus (Box 158)
      - Shibazaki, Hiromasa, interview (Box 158)
      - South Africa essay interviews (Box 158)
      - Thomas Jefferson portrait presentation, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Va. (Box 158)
      - Time Distribution Services (Box 158)
      - Time, inc. Creative Conference, Bermuda, 12 July (Box 158)
      - Time magazine statistics (Box 158)
      - Time magazine Update on America '77 conference, 16-19 Oct., (2 folders) (Box 158)
      - Woman magazine, (4 folders) (Box 158)
    - 1977-1978
      - Kennan, George (Box 159)
      - Woman magazine, (4 folders) (Box 159)
    - 1978
      - Alicia Patterson Foundation symposium on Zurcher v. Stanford Daily, 22 June (Box 159)
      - "Are We 'Destroying' Jimmy Carter?" 25 May (Box 159)
      - Barraclough, Geoffrey, reviews (Box 159)
      - Cronkite, Walter, Lord and Taylor Rose Award toast, 1 Nov. (Box 159)
      - Dinner for Prime Minister Constantine Caramanlis, 5 June (Box 159)
      - Editor in chief transition announcement (Box 159)
      - Friendship (Box 160)
      - Irredentism, (2 folders) (Box 160)
      - "The Katharine Graham Story," Washington Star, 13-17 Nov. (Box 160)
      - Legal (Box 160)
      - Lehnus, Donald J., "Who's On Time?: An Analytical Study of the Persons Who Have Appeared on the Covers of TIME from March 3, 1923 to January 3, 1977" (Box 160)
      - Penney-Missouri Awards, 1 Nov. (Box 160)
      - Role of the editor in chief (Box 160)
      - Time, inc. North Carolina Seminar, 11-13 Nov., (2 folders) (Box 161)
      - Time, inc. Second Creative Conference, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 18-21 June (Box 161)
      - Time, inc. Taxation Conference, Washington, D.C., 12-14 Sept., (4 folders) (Box 161)
      - Time magazine covers, (3 folders) (Box 162)
      - Time magazine National Security Issues Roundtable, 20 Feb. (Box 162)
      - Time magazine style guide (Box 162)
      - Twentieth Century Fund Task Force on International Flow of News, (4 folders) (Box 162)
      - White House dinner, 19 July (Box 163)
      - World Press Freedom Committee, (4 folders) (Box 163)
    - 1979
      - Annual Judicial Conference, Second Judicial Circuit, Buck Hill Falls, Penn. (Box 163)
      - Appointment as editor in chief, congratulatory notes, (1 folder) (Box 163)
      - Appointment as editor in chief, congratulatory notes, (3 folders) (Box 164)
      - Chicago, Ill.-Des Moines, Iowa trip, 14-17 Oct. (Box 164)
      - "Comparing Look to Life" report (Box 164)
      - Fidel Castro dinner, 13 Oct. (Box 164)
      - Ford, Gerald R., A Time to Heal (Box 164)
      - Fortune (Box 164)
      - Hedley Donovan retirement dinner, 30 May, (2 folders) (Box 164)
      - Kennedy, Edward M., dinner, 17 Oct. (Box 164)
      - Kissinger, Henry, dinner, New York, N.Y., 2 Oct. (Box 165)
      - Kissinger, Henry, memoirs (Box 165)
      - Legal (Box 165)